Be advised,
we are in a bad situation
that we can't really
get spots on ground.
Jimmy, hey,
we're on the west side,
left-hand side of the valley,
approaching one now.
Move!
Hey, Duff! Ford's been hit.
We gotta go back for him.
Let's move.
Duff, let's go! Come on!
Contact!
Let's go. Come on.
Hey. You're okay. Look at me.
Look at me.
You're okay. You're okay.
I need you to breathe.
Breathe.
Hey, we don't fucking die.
We don't fucking die.
Thanks a lot, brother.
What can I get you, papi?
Anything cold.
Yeah, that's right.
Go ahead, deal them up.
Fuck me.
You got a problem, chief?
No, no problem here.
I was wondering
if you could get one more in.
You got money, we'd be happy
to take it off you.
What's the buy-in?
Two hundred dollars.
What about this?
Make room for the stranger,
boys.
He just paid for a place.
Two hundred dollars.
Don't spend it all at once.
I see you, and I'm all in.
Quite a poker face you have,
chief.
Only face I got.
Hmm...
Just showed you my ball sack.
What you gonna do?
Heh, I'm a little light.
Yeah, you are.
The fuck
you think you're doing?
I'm winning.
Fucking son of a bitch.
You're a fucking cheater.
Give me the watch.
Try and take it,
asshole.
I think I'll just
let my boys decide.
Hey!
Jesus fucking Christ!
You are a bad motherfucker.
I can't kick your ass.
I should shoot you
right where you fucking stand.
I'm standing right here.
You ain't taking my bike.
You can keep
the fucking bike.
I'm taking my money
and I'm taking my watch.
You fucking guys are pathetic.
Jesus Christ!
How you doing?
Fosco.
Yeah, that's right.
It's Max. Uh-huh.
Yeah. I'm back in town, baby.
Hey, listen,
let me ask you a question.
Still having that,
uh, thing tomorrow?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'll be there.
And I'm bringing a friend
with me too.
-Hey.
I know you?
No, I, um, just wanted to--
All right,
we'll go with the hard sell.
All right, look.
The name's Max.
I was in the bar last night.
I saw you in action.
I gotta tell you, you got some
amazing skills, my friend.
So, look, how about this?
How about you let a brother
buy you breakfast
while you hear me out?
You know, some eggs, some bacon,
maybe a little chorizo.
Listen...
if you don't like
what I have to say,
if you're not interested,
then, hey,
we can just part ways.
No harm, no foul.
Besides, breakfast is the
cheapest meal of the day anyway.
I know you don't know me,
but I know fighters.
And that skillset you got there
could be a fucking gold mine...
if it were to be exploited
by the right per--
That's a great speech, man.
I got no desire
to be exploited.
-Just--
-My country did that.
All right,
look, just tell me...
how much money
did you make last night?
Enough.
Enough for what,
hmm?
One, maybe two more nights
in some shitty motel?
What if you could make enough
to stay in a decent place for,
I don't know, a month?
Maybe even more.
I would tell you that I'm not
one for laying down roots.
There has to be something
that you want, right?
Come on.
Something that you need.
Everybody needs
something.
I don't need anything, man.
Everything I need
is right in that bag.
Well I can tell you what you're
not gonna find in that bag.
Enlighten me.
An outlet.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
I saw you last night.
More importantly,
I saw that look in your face.
That look in your eyes.
You didn't just wanna
choke that clown out.
You wanted to make sure
he understood
that you had something
that you were trying
to prove to the world--
Hey, hey, hey. Don't think
that you fucking know me.
-I didn't say that I know you.
-Don't.
I didn't say
that I know you.
But I do know
that fucking look.
It's the same look
my brother had
when he came home
from Afghanistan.
It was probably
the same look he had
when he put that goddamn Glock
in his mouth
and he squeezed the trigger.
Last night I did
what I had to do. That's it.
Yeah. I understand that.
But you got a lot of anger
inside you...
and if you don't find a way
to let that shit out,
it's gonna eat you alive.
You're full of shit.
And if you don't get it out,
that shit will eat you alive.
-Mm-hm.
-Uh-huh.
You know, you are one
hard fucking sell,
my friend.
I don't even know
what you're selling.
Then why not let me show you?
♪ I'm the most selfish person
That I know, here we go ♪
Place your bet,
you fucking motherfuckers.
You degenerate assholes.
Ha-ha-ha!
Wanna tell me
what the hell's going on?
This, my friend,
this is your fucking outlet.
My outlet?
Is this what I think it is?
What do you want me to say, huh?
You know the first rule
of fight club.
Just wait here.
♪ And sowing what you reap
Know your worth ♪
-My man.
-Yo, Maxie, what's up?
-Hey, brother.
-How you doing, man?
Listen up, man.
I need to talk to you.
♪ I be shinin'
Perfect timin' ♪
♪ Check your watch
Watch, watch ♪
He's good, I'm telling you.
Okay?
Do me one solid.
All right.
All right, brother.
Okay, no more bets, assholes.
No more bets, pendejos.
That's it.
No more fucking bets.
Okay, come on.
Go! Get the fuck back there.
Come on.
It's my fucking turn to speak.
So you all know the rules.
The guy at the hospital
afterwards is the winner.
The loser is the guy
at the morgue.
In a real fight,
there are no fucking rules.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Are you ready?
So let's fucking fight!
Come on.
Yeah! That's right.
Too slow, bitch. Come on.
Yeah, yeah?
Yeah!
Get this piece of shit
out of here. Get him out.
You suck. You kidding me?
Get the fuck out.
Okay, now for those who aren't
already broke and destitute,
we got a special event.
You know Karloff.
Karloff!
Hold on! Hold on. No!
Hey, hey! Shut the fuck up.
I know some of you are eager
to put your money on this guy,
on the big boy,
aka Frankenstein's monster.
But you know what?
We have an unknown quantity
for you
to risk
your hard-earned cash on.
Today, I'm gonna give you--
Maxie,
what's your boy's name?
Oh, shit. What the hell
is your name, anyway?
-Come on, spit it out.
-No fucking way.
-What are you talking about?
Can't leave me standing here.
I bought you breakfast.
-Bought me fucking breakfast?
-Yeah.
Cheapest meal
of the fucking day.
No harm, no foul.
No fucking way.
Oh, oh. Looks like we have
ourselves a fucking pussy here.
Is that it?
Are you a wet fucking pussy?
You fucking coward!
You heard me.
You're a fucking coward.
You know what, guys?
If he stays,
I'll give you 10-to-1
on the wet pussy.
Do your thing.
You degenerate motherfuckers.
Go get him.
-Easy fucking money, Max.
-Uh-huh.
You should get
your head examined.
Yeah.
Yeah! Yeah! Yes!
-Son of a bitch.
-Yes! Yes! Ha, ha!
Easy fucking money, huh?
Yeah, my ass. Pay up.
Come on. Thank you.
Fuck.
-Hey, hold up.
-Cop car!
Motherfucker!
Rolled just in time, baby.
Don't make me regret this.
What you got to regret, huh?
You just kicked
some fucking ass.
♪ Ah, are you mad to see
My hand raised? ♪
♪ Tell the truth, do I make you
Feel some type of way? ♪
♪ You see this winnin' doesn't
Interrupt your grinnin' ♪
♪ Are you waiting for the judge
To try to sing somewhere foul ♪
Oh, I almost forgot.
Here you go.
What's this?
-Your winnings.
-My winnings?
Yeah. For the fight.
I didn't place a bet.
I did, on your behalf.
You used my fucking money?
Look, you handed me
your bag.
I saw the money inside,
all right?
Fosco was offering 10-to-1
on you winning.
I saw your skills.
I knew you couldn't lose.
-My skills.
-Mm-hm.
So why didn't you use
your own money?
I would have,
except I spent all of mine
buying you breakfast.
Oh, and, uh,
just for full transparency,
I took a little
commission on that.
For, you know,
administrative costs.
-Administrative costs?
-Mm-hm.
Hey, uh...
You got a place to stay in L.A.?
Nah, not yet.
All right, well don't worry
about that. I've got you.
Oh, well,
if you got me...
I feel much better.
I'm glad you do.
♪ Waitin' on a bag
I'm sittin' on a brick ♪
♪ Thinkin' on my past
I'm glad it's what I did ♪
♪ But you're movin' fast
Waitin' on the list ♪
♪ Why you gettin' mad
Because we gettin' chips ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock
Your lights out... ♪
What is wrong with you?
What are you looking for?
-Baby, what are you looking for?
-Nothing. Nothing!
I'm not looking for anything,
baby. Just watch out.
It's all good.
-It's all good, baby.
-Mom?
Did you take my stuff?
What? What are you
talking about?
-Did you take my stuff?
-Calm down.
-Mom!
-Oh, baby.
-You ass!
-Don't touch me.
-Go! Get out! Get the fuck out!
-No! Come on. No!
Mom?
Get the fuck out! Get out!
Get out!
-Baby! Baby!
-Get the fuck out!
-Hey!
-No!
Stan, get the fuck
out of my house.
-Hey! Hey! What's this?
-You can't do this.
Who the fuck are you, man?
Get the fuck out of here.
-You okay?
-I'm fine.
-You sure?
-Hey.
-When the fuck did you get out?
Just in time.
Who the fuck is it?
Fuck.
-What's up, Stan?
-No, man. Fuck.
The fuck you going, Stan?
I'm packing
to come see fucking Sage.
It's all good.
Let's go. Sage is waiting.
It's good. It's good.
Go ahead, I'll follow you.
♪ Wanna see through my eyes
♪ Where I've been
♪ Am I playin', am I playin'
I don't give
a fuck.
I don't give a fuck.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on, man.
I don't wanna...
Do we have to go there?
I know what the fuck is--
Let's go.
♪ Got cold without me
Without me ♪
♪ Coming back from a
grave revival ♪
♪ Wanna see through my eyes
♪♪ Where I've been
♪ Am I playin', am I playin'
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, Stan.
Stan the Man.
How you doing, baby?
Sage.
Good to see you.
Yeah, heh,
good to see you, Stan.
-We got a problem.
-Yeah, we do.
There's a problem?
Yeah.
The problem is
your books are light.
There's a shitload
of money missing
and nobody's telling me
anything.
So, what the fuck?
Where's my money?
Are we talking about my money?
Now, see here?
You make me look bad
in front of the company.
You both got it all wrong,
though.
Oh, good,
so there's no problem.
I've got your money.
It's just--
Whoa, you fucking bitch.
Sage, come on. You know me.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Just...
It's all right, baby.
It's your lucky day.
Hi.
Come here.
If you tell me the truth,
I won't be upset.
Come on, Stan.
Think, fucker.
I know where it is.
It's at
my girlfriend's house.
We can go get it right now.
We can get in my car and go.
Do you know
what he's talking about?
Please.
Good. Then you clean up
the fucking mess.
Fuck me! Come on.
He was an earner.
If you don't get me
my fucking money,
you'll be dealing with people
that make me look
like Snow White.
Okay, how am I supposed to get
the money from him now?
Handle the fucking body.
-Are we good?
-No, we're fucking not.
The money?
I don't wanna
fucking talk about it.
Kincaid.
Shit.
Give us 20 minutes.
Gang shooting, six dead.
Shocker.
Look at you.
Building and fixing things.
Well, Max said
I had to earn my keep.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, I fixed your sink too.
It had no pressure.
What? That's amazing, thank you.
You're welcome.
It's nice to have
some real help around here.
Oh, and I fixed
your bathroom light.
You're welcome.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
Get-- Go in the house.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Sage.
Max Bomer.
I heard you were out.
Yeah. Made parole
about two weeks ago.
Two weeks?
-Uh-huh.
-Man, that's a long time.
I thought
we were friends, Max.
I didn't hear from you once.
You didn't call.
You didn't DM me.
I was on the road,
all right?
But I'm here now.
Yes, you are.
Where's my fucking money?
Now, look, obviously
it's not all of it.
But it's just, you know,
a good faith gesture, you know.
-Oh, is that it?
-Yeah.
That's nice.
I appreciate that.
I don't think
it's gonna cut it, though,
because it's like 39 short.
Thirty-nine?
No, no, no.
When I went away, it was 20.
You think the juice stopped
when you went inside?
Max, you know, they wanted
to fuck you up
when you were in there,
and I wouldn't let them,
you know why?
You're a fucking
degenerate,
but you're a degenerate
with a heart of gold,
who loves his family
and wouldn't want anything
to happen to them.
Don't even think about
going near my family.
Keep them out of it.
Huh, this buys you one week.
Why don't you let me
earn it?
-In the ring.
-No, those days are gone, Max.
I'm not talking about me.
I got a guy.
-Huh.
-He's good. He's real good.
Now, look, all I need
is one fight to prove it.
Yeah. Uh...
-Hey, Carter.
-Yeah, boss?
What do you say?
What's that?
Should we give
our old friend here a break?
I say you let me beat his ass,
throw him in the fucking river.
Yes. The guy's hardcore.
Come on. Look, just--
I don't know. Give me 3-to-1.
My guy against
any one of your guys.
You sure you wanna take
that kind of bet against me?
What have I got to lose?
You could always pick
fighters, Max.
Thank you.
Can't bet sports for shit,
but we wouldn't be here
if you could.
Well, all right.
I'll set you up one fight,
3-to-1.
-That's a bet.
-All right.
Who's this fighter
you're talking about?
You wouldn't know him.
♪ I feel like a millionaire
♪ Word up
♪ ...back to California
♪ Like E-40, stay sharp
On every damn corner ♪
♪ Small-time hustlers
Wanna act rich ♪
♪ Stay local while I got
A country on my back, bitch ♪
♪ Prob a legend
In my 'hood, boy... ♪
That's my dad's bag.
His left hook
was better, though.
Ha! What you know
about boxing?
He taught me
a little something.
Oh, he taught you
a little something?
Yeah.
It's good on him
for doing that.
Yeah, well, he died.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Must have been tough for you.
Hannah, baby,
I need you to empty all the
trash when you come in, please.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Thank you.
-You hungry?
-I'm always hungry.
Good.
Dinner will be ready soon.
Sweet kid you got there.
Yeah, I know.
-Something smells good.
-Thanks.
Oh, I left some fresh towels
out for you.
Okay. Thanks.
Um-hum. You're welcome.
Thank you, really.
For what?
Taking me in.
I feel like a stray.
I always had love
for the strays.
Ever since I was little,
actually.
I remember there was
this cute little puppy
that used to run around
the neighborhood.
And I wanted to keep it
so bad,
but my dad would not
let me have it.
So I hid it and I fed it
for two weeks.
Did he change his mind?
No. He took it to the pound
and had it put to sleep.
-No.
-Said it was
to teach me a lesson.
-Oh, that's rough.
-It was.
-Did it?
-No.
I still got love
for the stray.
Hey.
Well, look who decided
to show up.
I missed it.
-Mm. You did.
-You did.
At the dinner table.
-I'm sorry about that.
-Uh-huh.
Since you've been gone,
Duffy fixed almost ten things.
At least.
You should have seen him.
He was like
Bob the Builder.
Well, thank you for
helping my Ra.
-Still the same old Max.
-Mm-hm.
Hannah, will you help me
do the dishes, please?
-Please?
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Smells good.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
-It was good.
-It was great.
-That's a good family, man.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Where you been?
You wanna know
where I've been?
-Yeah.
-You sure?
Yeah.
I've been setting up
the next things.
-The next thing?
-Uh-huh.
Man, we haven't done
the first thing.
Listen, I talked to my guy.
He says he can get us in
on these next fights.
I'm talking bigger venues,
bigger money.
-Your guy?
-Yeah.
The next fights.
More truck-stop bullshit?
-No. No, Duffy listen.
-I'm not doing it.
Just listen to me for a second,
all right?
It ain't that. We talking about
real fucking money here.
Real money.
And like I told you before,
I know fighters.
These bums, they're not even
in your league, man.
We can take this shit.
We?
Yeah, we. You know,
it's a team effort.
Yeah, man, it makes sense.
I get punched in the face,
you get paid.
Hey, we all gotta do
what we gotta do.
Yeah, cheers.
♪ You can cast me...
She's one
of my best fighters.
I put together 20 for you.
Feels light.
Yeah. Well,
I'm working on it.
I'm thinking tonight,
we'll bring in 150,
easy.
Thank you.
I appreciate
you doing this, man.
It's cool.
You win this thing,
I could finally be
out of debt
from this dickhead.
Be free and clear for the first
time in a long time.
Just stay
free and clear.
-Is this your guy?
-Yeah.
You look like a tough fuck.
You a middleweight?
You think you got
what it takes?
-We'll see.
I think we said 3-to-1,
right, Max?
Yeah.
Let's say 5-to-1.
Oh, well,
the agreement was three.
Well, it's 5-to-1
or I'm gonna walk.
This guy...
He's got balls, huh?
He's got skills
to back it.
Skills too? You got skills
to pay the bills?
Why don't you place the bet
and find out?
5-to-1?
I'm down with it.
Let's go.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
All right, all right,
all right. Yeah.
We got new faces
for you here tonight.
No, no, no.
Trust me on this one.
I've seen both of these two,
and they're
the real fucking contenders.
You're in for
a fucking treat. Seriously.
So you know the rules.
You fight
until one of you drops.
There are no fucking tap-outs.
We got that?
Got it? Got it?
Let's fucking fight!
No! No!
Come on!
Yes! Let's go! Keep it going!
Yes! Yes!
♪ I did it all on my own
♪ Ain't need no help
I keep it in the zone ♪
♪ I'm so proud
I do it all alone ♪
That's what I'm talking about,
goddamn it.
Yes! That's what the fuck
I'm trying to say.
Congratulations.
I fucking told you, Sage.
I fucking told you.
Hey, knock this win
off my principal.
Understood.
You made me eat my words.
What can I say?
But just give me
another chance.
-A chance for what?
-To win my money back.
You against Carter.
No, no, no.
What you say, cowboy?
He ain't no fucking cowboy.
What odds?
Hey, Duffy,
listen to me.
You don't have
to do this shit, man.
-Double or nothing.
-Triple.
It's triple or nothing,
he keeps all his money,
he walks away.
You're a beast.
You got me feeling
all warm and fuzzy.
-You good?
-Yeah.
You got a deal.
Where and when?
Here and now.
Let's do it.
♪ I'm on top
♪ I never stop
Come on!
Enough! Enough!
Come on! Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop! Stop! You got him.
All right? All right?
You got him, man.
I gotta tell you, Duffy,
you are one
bad motherfucker, man,
but let me tell you something.
This is what I noticed.
You're a little flat-footed when
you're throwing your punches.
You know what I'm saying?
You need to get on
the balls of them feet,
generate more power that way.
-Is that right?
-I'm telling you.
Here you go.
-Lion's share.
-Wow.
Let me ask you something,
and this is real talk here.
Why are you in L.A.?
-Why am I in L.A.?
-Yeah.
It's a family thing.
My mother, she...
She died suddenly
a couple years back.
Oh.
I wasn't here.
Nobody was here for her.
Sorry to hear that.
So they put her
in some hole somewhere.
Alone.
Anyway, I'm gonna get her
a headstone.
I'm gonna get a piece of land
and she's gonna rest in peace.
That's why I'm in L.A.
Sounds like you're doing
the right thing by her.
Underneath it all,
you're a good dude, Duffy.
Maybe that's why you met me.
-Maybe.
Get some rest, man.
Hello?
I got the address
to Stan's girl.
-Rachel Bomer?
-Yeah?
We're looking for
Stanley Lazare.
He's not here.
We're gonna have to
search your home.
Not without a warrant.
Fuck. Go.
-Come on.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-Don't touch me.
-Step aside.
What? You can't
just walk in my house.
Don't touch her!
Hannah, come here.
Take a seat, both of you!
Keep going.
Everything. Everything.
Let's go. Tear it apart.
The kid's room. All of it.
Fuck it.
Somebody get out there.
Motherfucking shit.
-Get the kid's room.
-I'll go.
All right, let's go. Let's go!
Keep looking.
What's that?
Check that fucking shit.
The house is clean.
Fuck.
You're a smart woman, Rachel.
And a mom.
You want what's best
for her, right?
Hey, look at me.
Your boyfriend Stan...
he's a piece of shit.
It's in your best interest
to find the money.
God, it's so fucking hard
to be a mother.
There's never enough time.
It's okay, baby.
Take it easy.
Where's my money, Rufus?
I'm just gonna need
a little bit more time, okay?
-Wrong answer.
-Jesus!
Fuck, you're making
a mess, Rufus.
All right! All right!
Take it easy.
All right.
-Let's go! Come on.
-Okay.
Here. Take this.
It's all I got right now.
-What is that?
-I'm gonna have the
rest next week, okay?
-Next week?
-No!
Tomorrow.
Or this is gonna feel
like a fucking massage.
♪ Standin' on
The battleground, yeah ♪
♪ It's time
To put the foot down yeah ♪
You missed a spot.
No shit.
Friends downtown
are concerned.
That's nice.
Their concern doesn't really
fucking help, though, does it?
I'm just the messenger, pal.
Your partner
is out of control.
Her judgment is fucked.
I heard you ran into a little
trouble with one of your CIs.
-You remember Stan Lazare?
-Yeah. That piece of shit.
Word is he's cleaning money
for Sage Parker.
Well, he was.
Until we trusted him to move
some money for an associate.
And then six figures
went missing.
What kind of associate?
Friends from down south.
How much you owe?
Hola, Ridgway.
You've been a tough woman
to track down.
Five hundred K.
We got less than a week
to cover it.
Five hundred?
Friends from the south?
-Got any accounts you can tax?
-Nothing that big, that fast.
Where does Sage come in on this?
It's on him too.
I'm working on
a couple of things
to try to come up
with it.
Okay.
My patience is running out.
-It's handled.
-Good.
I would hate to have
to hear about you on the news.
Like I said, it's handled.
I've got a crew. Six guys.
Straight fucking killers
with badges.
You can trust them.
If the money's right,
we got your back.
Make that happen.
Tick-tock.
Oh, fuck.
-You okay?
-You all right?
No, I'm not okay.
Look at this place.
Holy shit.
They came in here.
They destroyed everything.
Why? What'd they say?
-They were looking for Stan.
-Stan?
What is this guy into?
He owned a dry cleaners.
That's all I know.
That's it?-Yes.
What else did they say?
They said they were
looking for money.
And they asked
about somebody named Sage.
You know somebody named Sage?
Sage.
Max, is he
coming back here?
Is he coming back?
What do I do, Max?
Look, just, um...
You just sit tight,
all right?
Just listen to me.
Listen to me.
Just sit tight. Lock the door.
We'll be right back, okay?
Just lock the door.
I'll call you.
No cops.
Don't let anybody in.
Okay?
Yo!
Where's Sage at?
I wouldn't.
He's in the office, man.
Come on, man.
-Hey. What the fuck?
-What the fuck?
You send the cops to my house
and rough up my family?
-No, I didn't do shit.
-That's bullshit.
They fucked up my house.
They roughed up my sister!
-What are you talking about?
-They threatened her!
No, that ain't me.
But I do know
Stan still owes a lot of money
to people much more
dangerous than I am.
If you wanna mess with them,
go on, go on ahead.
But it went missing
from your sister's house, Max.
If you're not
responsible for it,
who do you think
will be?
Listen to me,
just keep your people
away from my family.
All right, well, I'll call off
the dogs, if you pay the debt.
-And you come fight for me.
-Never gonna happen.
All right, I'll give you
48 hours to decide.
After that, the outcome's
beyond my control, believe me.
Sage, you know what?
Fuck this.
Oh, Max, come on.
We're friends.
I love you, man.
You want another shot
at the title, big man?
You got lucky.
-You got this, baby.
-Yeah.
Hello.
Do I know you?
I know you.
Call me if you want
to level up.
Level up?
What the fuck?
What kind of cops
do you got here?
Goddamn it.
What the fuck
is going on here?
I don't know, man, but
these are bad fucking cops.
Your sister's
in trouble, Max.
Hey, I--
I appreciate
everything,
but you don't have to
do this, all right?
This is my fight.
This is our fight.
It's our fight.
Come on.
-What the fuck you doing here?
-I need a fight, ASAP.
Yeah, well,
you better keep looking.
Fosco. What you got
for me, man?
You're not a good person
to be seen with right now, Max.
Sage will hand me my ass
just for talking to you.
He wants payback.
Yeah, and I'm trying to get
him that payback.
So what is he,
all of a sudden
hurting to put fists
in the ring?
Come on, man.
Between you and I,
we both know
he's not the only one
putting on fights
in this town.
What about that lady?
You really wanna go there?
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
-I owe you one.
-I'll remember you said that.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
Can you breathe?
Put this in the wound.
Breathe.
You're gonna walk out of here.
Look at me.
Duffy, keep the pressure on him.
I'll lift him forward.
It's gonna fucking hurt.
Are you ready?
-Three, two, one, go.
-Fuck!
Okay. Okay.
-I want you to stay calm. Relax.
-All right. All right.
-It's nothing.
-We're gonna go out of here.
Huh.
We're gonna take him
out of here.
Yeah. We're gonna get you
Yeah.
Ford?
We got you, buddy.
-We got you, old boy.
-Hey, hey.
Shit.
-We gotta go. We gotta go.
-Goddamn it.
We gotta get him
back to his family, Duff.
We gotta get him back
to his fucking family, okay?
Come on. Come on.
Up!
Hey.
Can't sleep either, huh?
-No. Did I wake you?
-No. No.
I'm up all night.
That Hannah, that girl can
sleep through an earthquake.
-You're fine.
-Okay, good.
Thank you. For everything.
Fixing the house.
I appreciate you.
You're welcome.
So tell me about you.
What was it like
being in the military?
It was all right at first.
I was really young
when I joined.
I was gonna
change the world.
Really?
Yeah.
Till the world changed me.
How so?
Well, I mean,
I saw some bad things,
you know.
You don't see the worst
parts of humanity
over and over and over again
and not be affected,
not be screwed up.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I lost
a lot of good friends.
A lot of good brothers.
I see their faces every night
when I close my eyes.
Every, every single night.
I can't escape it.
That's why I keep moving.
So...
That's my sad story.
It's not that sad.
Come on.
What can I do for you, Fosco?
The question is,
what can I do for you?
Well,
I'm seriously intrigued.
-Duffy.
-What about him?
You want to know
the shit about him?
Well, uh--
Word on the street is...
he's put a major dent
in your payroll
and he's made you look
like a fool.
You think I look like
a fool, Fosco?
Well, would I be here
if I did?
Right.
Max is desperate
for another fight.
He wants high stakes.
Fine. Fuck it.
Let's give him what he wants.
See if he can fight
with the big dogs.
♪ So you wanna be a rap star?
♪ Fast money, fast women
Fast cars ♪
♪ Dress rappers
It could be a rat race... ♪
The real shit.
You ready?
♪ So you wanna be a rap star?
♪ Fast money, fast women
Fast cars ♪
-Fosco!
-Yo.
What the fuck?
You really do
owe me one, Max.
I had call in
more than one favor
to get you
through those doors.
Hey, don't worry about it.
You're gonna get your cut.
-Yeah?
-Sage will get his too.
Your boy's
gotta win first.
♪ We didn't even
Ask permission ♪
♪ I brought the flame
All validifying in the soul ♪
♪ Yes, I knew...
Buy-in's in there.
I threw in a little bit
for Santiago.
'Cause I like you.
What do you know
about this guy?
Well, he's slower than you,
there's no doubt about that.
But he'll try to use
his weight on you.
He'll try to tie you up.
Make sure you keep it moving.
Stay on your toes.
Yeah.
The guy you're about to fight
is a fucking cop.
What?
He's as dirty as it comes,
so watch out for anything, okay?
A fight's a fight.
All right.
I should handcuff you
to that fucking pole behind me.
Well, as much as I like
the sound of that,
if you're talking about
Stan the Man,
the guy's a piece of shit.
He was skimming.
He paid for it. He's gone.
I don't think you really
understand. The house was clean.
It's on you.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is on both of us,
detective.
If you're thinking about
coming down on me hard,
I'll only come down
on you harder.
Twenty-year decorated LAPD
detective Ellen Ridgway...
with dope and money
and the gangs and cartels.
That sounds like
some front-page shit to me.
I got the pics.
High resolution and
everything.
Are you ready tonight?
Are you fucking ready tonight
for a fight?
Fighters.
The rules are
there no rules.
Tonight, these gladiators
are fighting for blood.
They're fighting for respect.
They're fighting for you.
So let's fucking fight!
Let's go Duff.
Let's go! Come on, come on.
Watch out!
Come on. Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Yes!
Bullshit!
Oh shit!
-Come on.
-Come on!
Yes! Yes!
It's all good. Yes!
Yes!
-Yes!
-We got a winner!
Winner!
Shit. What the fuck
just happened?
What the fuck just happened?
Your boy just killed
a fucking cop.
That's what the fuck
just happened.
LAPD!
Everyone clear
the fucking place out now!
Get the fuck out!
I'm getting my ass
out of fucking town
before Ridgway
finds me,
because she'll want your beating
heart on a fucking plate.
Let's go.
Get the hell out of here.
Santiago was undercover.
Gang-related killing.
Put that in the report.
He was a good fucking cop.
He was one of us.
Sage is
blackmailing us.
Says he has
pictures of us
coming out of
the O'Sullivan case.
Then
fuck him too.
Just make sure nothing
comes back to haunt us.
Okay.
Shit, Mom,
you could have knocked.
You start paying rent,
then I'll start knocking.
-You wanna explain this to me?
-Shit.
"Shit"?
Hannah, what is this doing
in our house?
Ask that piece of shit
that you're dating.
Excuse me?
You know it's true.
I mean, he is.
Look at the way
that he treats you.
He had this money in the house,
knowing that we need it,
and that we're always behind,
always struggling.
Hannah.
And he just forgot
that it was there
because he's high
all the time.
I hate him!
I hate that you're with him.
I hate
the way that he treats you.
I hate that he acts that way
towards you.
-You don't deserve that.
-Okay, baby.
-I was just trying to help.
-I know. I know. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for those cops
to mess up the house.
Baby, look at me.
Look, wait.
I didn't want anyone
to get hurt.
-It is not your fault.
-I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
-I love you.
It's okay.
-Max?
-Listen to me.
I need you to pack
some things right now.
Be ready in 15 minutes.
We're almost there.
-What are you talking about?
-I'll explain when we get there.
Wait, Max, listen.
We found the money.
Well, you might as well
keep it. You're gonna need it.
Just be ready to leave
as soon as we get there.
All right, bye. Pack up.
We gotta go.
-What?
-Pack up. Come on, let's go.
Mom!
It's Kincaid. Shots fired.
Wabash and Fourth.
Armed suspect on the premises.
Send backup.
Go, go, go!
What the fuck is going on?
In the car.
-Hannah, let's go.
-Come on. Move!
Rachel, come on! Get in the
goddamn car. We gotta go now!
What is going on, Max?
Down!
-Mom!
-Call 911!
All right. Come on. Call 911!
-All right, all right.
Look at me.
-Fuck, fuck me.
Look at me, Hannah. You're okay,
baby. You're okay. Look at me.
Yeah, listen.
My niece has been shot.
Just send someone
the hell down here right now.
B-O-M-E-R.
Yes. Hannah Bomer.
I'm her uncle.
Just hurry the hell up.
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
-How far?
-Just hang on.
They're just
two minutes out. Okay?
The ambulance
is two minutes away, baby.
-I don't wanna die.
-You're not gonna die, baby.
You're not gonna die.
Where the fuck are they?
We need to end this
tonight.
Let's do it.
Let me get your phone.
For what?
I'm gonna call somebody
that may be able to help us.
Duff!
Hey.
Don't you fucking sneak up
on me like that.
-Heh, how you doing, Duff?
-How are you?
Look at you, mate.
Haven't changed a bit.
-How you doing, mate?
-Hey.
That's Max.
That's who I'm talking about.
Max. I'm Don.
Nice to meet you.
Take a seat.
You guys want a beer?
-Sure.
-Yeah?
-Fucking hell.
-How you been, man?
You know, getting by.
Look at you.
Look at you, man. Fuck me.
-How long's it been?
-About seven years.
-Fuck off.
-Yeah.
I'm not counting or anything,
but yeah.
I tried to get
in contact with you.
You did?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, I went through a thing,
you know.
Yeah. Nah.
It's all right, mate.
Thank you.
Did he fill you in on, uh,
all this guy's accomplishments
and the legend that is
Duffy?
-Not a clue.
-Fucking legend.
Saved my ass at
least twice. Right?
-Probably more.
-Probably.
Yeah.
One time in Kenya.
Yeah, you remember that?
And then, uh...
Mogadishu.
Moga-fucking-dishu. Yeah.
Lucky to get out of that place
in one piece.
Maybe.
So, uh, ahem, you wanna tell me
what's going down?
Going through the shit, man.
His sister is--
His niece is in trouble.
We're dealing with
some crooked fucking cops.
-The worst kind.
-It's bad.
We need guns. We need gear.
We need it tonight.
Well, uh...
there's something in the car.
In the car, heh?
Yeah, I got something
in the car.
I wasn't sure exactly
what you needed,
so I brought a few options.
-Yeah, you did.
-We appreciate this.
Hey, don't worry.
For this guy, whatever you need.
-Fuck.
-I owe you, brother.
You don't owe me, mate.
-So when do we leave?
-We?
You got nothing
to do with this, man.
I fucking do now.
This isn't your fight brother.
Since when was
any of the shit
that we did over there
our fight?
It was never
our fucking fight, was it?
Right now, I got a mate
who needs my fucking help.
So whether you like it or not,
I'm coming with you.
Besides, I'm bored
out of my fucking mind.
They're here.
Green means go.
My lead, through the front.
Riggs, through the back.
Remember,
no arrests tonight,
no paperwork.
Toe tags for everyone.
-Hey! Hey!
-Where is he? Where is he?
-Fuck you.
-Where is he?
-Where's Sage? Sage!
We had a fucking deal. I fight,
you leave his family alone.
And I did. What the fuck
you talking about?
The drive-by.
The drive-by at my house,
you fucking asshole.
-They shot my niece!
-I didn't do--
What you think this
shit is funny, huh?
It's Ridgway.
-Fuck her.
-Where is she?
Where is she?
-Ridgway's a cop.
-I don't give a fuck.
Santiago was a cop.
She's cleaning up loose ends.
We're all fucked.
Light them up!
Max?
Baby!
-Are you okay?
-I love you, Lynx.
Baby, are you okay?
I didn't do shit.
I know you didn't do shit.
Max!
You good?
-Max!
-Drop the fucking gun
or I'll shoot him
in the head.
-Fuck.
-Drop the fucking gun!
All right, all right.
All right.
How are you gonna
get out of this?
It's what I do, Duffy.
It's too bad Sage fucked up.
We could have had some fun.
Fuck off.
-You good?
-Yeah, yeah.
Ugh... Fuck!
Am I dying?
I can't...
-Come on.
-All right. Yeah.
-Let me see.
-Fuck.
The goddamn thing
actually works. Huh!
Oh, fuck.
You're all right.
You are all right, man.
Sorry, brother.
I'm sorry, brother.
You got nothing to be
sorry about.
All right. All right.
All right. Look at me.
Walk you out of here.
-Duff?
-Yeah.
I'm gonna walk you out of here.
I'll walk you out of here.
-Duff?
-Yeah.
I missed you, man.
I missed you.
I missed you too.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
You okay?
-Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
-Okay, good.
Hey, Duff, come on, man.
We gotta go.
Go, man. You go.
Get out of here.
No.
Listen to me.
We go together.
That's it.
Together.
Okay.
All right.
Morning, John.
We are live
here in downtown,
where last night
police are saying
a massive shootout took place
between local law enforcement
and drug traffickers.
At least ten are dead,
including veteran detectives
Ray Kincaid and Ellen Ridgway,
who tragically lost their lives
in the line of duty.
Ridgway was
a highly decorated officer,
who,
according to the department,
served her district
with passion and honor.
And her loss will leave a void
in the community she served
for years to come.
Hey Rachel, it's Duff.
Look, I just wanted to
say thank you.
Looking out for me, you know,
taking in a stranger.
I appreciate it.
Sorry I won't be there for
Hannah when she wakes up but...
She is strong, like her momma.
She'll be fine.
Anyway, I got to take
off for a while.
Till this whole thing dies down.
You know cops,
they look out for cops.
Good or bad.
As for the money...
I took what I needed for a
proper headstone for my mom.
Somewhere, I know she's
gonna be happy.
Keep the rest for you guys.
Keep Max out of trouble.
He's a good man.
Keep that spare room ready,
okay?
You never know when I might
pop in to see you guys.
I'll see you again.
Duff.
♪ Waitin' on a bag
I'm sittin' on a brick ♪
♪ Thinkin' on my past
I'm glad it's what I did ♪
♪ But you're movin' fast
Waitin' on the list ♪
♪ Why you gettin' mad
Because we gettin' chips ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ Hey, y'all ain't fuckin'
With us ♪
♪ Now we ain't fuckin'
Wit' y'all ♪
♪ You get that
Billy Bass treatment ♪
♪ If you bustin' my balls
What drugs? ♪
♪ If I'm in the place
I wanted 'em all ♪
♪ I'll take enough
To get away ♪
♪ Through every other
Withdrawal ♪
♪ Better watch it when I drop
It's the Apocalypse ♪
♪ Think you hot? You not
♪ Well, you hip hop
I don't miss ♪
♪ I done been at the bottom
With my bottom bitch ♪
♪ Somehow
Still got out of it ♪
♪ Where I'm from
We workin' 24-hour shifts ♪
♪ I got superpowers, kinda hard
When everybody powerless ♪
♪ Swear the people talk
As if ♪
♪ They standin' on
A pile o' shit ♪
♪ My past had to be a lesson
Felt like a life sentence ♪
♪ It's hunting season
♪ Before I'll be handling
The right weapon ♪
♪ I might check 'em, a matter
fact, I'ma mic check 'em ♪
♪ Darkness
To the everlasting light ♪
♪ Inside the light spectrum
♪ I'll break 'em down
And dissect 'em ♪
♪ If you feelin' froggy
Stay and leap ♪
♪ If not
Then get off my green ♪
♪ I know talk is cheap, but I
Was taught to get off my feet ♪
♪ Before I die on my back
Or ever live on my knees ♪
♪ And all this weed
That I breathe ♪
♪ I could 'chieve
In my sleep ♪
♪ To where I'm high enough
♪ That I'm gonna believe
In my dreams ♪
♪ Lock lock lock
Lock and load ♪
♪ Quarter-size optimal
♪ Rock the show
Then I gots to go ♪
♪ Hoppin' round the globe
♪ Yeah, starvin' artist
Lately, I've been eatin' more ♪
♪ Killers movin' silent
So tell me why I'ma... ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ I'm a wordsmith
To the wordless ♪
♪ Picture-perfect
♪ Billion-dollar baby says
Birth, I'll be worth it ♪
♪ Work it, gotta keep
My word, I'll be certain ♪
♪ No, I ain't worried
'Bout 'em yeah ♪
♪ They been surfin' my way
♪ Yeah, I fund the vague
Raised on the blades ♪
♪ Still win the game
If I played on one leg ♪
♪ And I still win the race
If I came the wrong way ♪
♪ Prayed on Sundays, I'ma stray
From gunplay survival ♪
♪ Underfit
Not the one that quit ♪
♪ Give it 101 percent
Nothing under it ♪
♪ Poker face
I just want the chips ♪
♪ I been hustlin'
Them customers ♪
♪ Until they come again
For them supplements ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we said ♪
♪ I'll knock your lights out
Yeah, when the light's out ♪
♪ Yeah
It's the illest shit we did ♪